{
    "id": "9c9e9199917f40be877a5d2b182b2708",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "My mother ………………….. up at 5 am. (Habitual action in the past)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gets",
                "got",
                "used to get"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f2f1d06798e842aeb5982c7d21f61640"
        },
        {
            "question": "Worldly pleasures ………………….. temporary. (General truth)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "were",
                "have been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4518fe5f655b42fd915eeb0ead8c7257"
        },
        {
            "question": "Portia …………………… that mercy is a divine quality. (General truth)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "says",
                "said",
                "has said"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "82dcb2c63fdf451a9ae379d523deac78"
        },
        {
            "question": "They …………………… for the program. (Action in progress)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have rehearsed",
                "are rehearsing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6bf7e7c281444875b9feb497ae5167e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "None of us …………………. Shakespeare.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "seen",
                "have seen"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e022e1dbe5a84ab0ae903f550df30fb1"
        },
        {
            "question": "His father ………………… last month. (Completed action)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "died",
                "has died",
                "had died"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "504c4126f5564ca1b20c6c32ae745114"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. ready. (Action going on at the moment of speaking)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "got",
                "was getting",
                "am getting"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "90ad7f3d44e34749923eb2625473dbbb"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I was young, I …………………. football every day. (Habitual action in the past)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was playing",
                "have played",
                "used to play"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "044f2358b98849238a518cd89d5fa755"
        },
        {
            "question": "When we …………………. a thief ………………….. into our house.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "slept, broke",
                "were sleeping, broke",
                "are sleeping, breaks"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f70660ca8fa942afa9452d8f2d28f6ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I ………………… hard, I ………………… (Unfulfilled condition)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "worked, would pass",
                "had worked, would have passed",
                "have worked, will have passed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4bac57a40d3e44a98fa6b4a651e1d587"
        }
    ]
}